
[
	{"question": "newspaper", "answer": "Die Zeitung", "learned": false, "chunk": 0},
	{"question": "bicycle", "answer": "Das Fahrrad", "learned": false, "chunk": 0},
	{"question": "cat", "answer": "Die Katze", "learned": false, "chunk": 0},
	{"question": "dog", "answer": "Der Hund", "learned": false, "chunk": 0},
	{"question": "고양이", "answer": "Die Katze", "learned": false, "chunk": 0}, 
	{"question": "flute", "answer": "Die Flöte", "learned": false, "chunk": 0},
	{"question": "BigMac", "answer": "BigMax", "learned": false, "chunk": 1},
	{"question": "물", "answer": "Das Wasser", "learned": false, "chunk": 1}, 
	{"question": "고양이", "answer": "Die Katze", "learned": false, "chunk": 1}, 
	{"question": "말", "answer": "Das Pferd", "learned": false, "chunk": 1}, 
	{"question": "배", "answer": "Das Schiff", "learned": false, "chunk": 1}, 
	{"question": "집", "answer": "Das Haus", "learned": false, "chunk": 1},
	{"question": "trousers", "answer": "Die Hose", "learned": false, "chunk": 2},
	{"question": "rose", "answer": "Die Rose", "learned": false, "chunk": 2}, 
	{"question": "trombone", "answer": "Die Posaune", "learned": false, "chunk": 2}, 
	{"question": "guitar", "answer": "Die Gitarre", "learned": false, "chunk": 2}, 
	{"question": "man", "answer": "Der Mann", "learned": false, "chunk": 2}, 
	{"question": "women", "answer": "Die Frau", "learned": false, "chunk": 2}
]

